CONTACT

- zackowen15@gmail.com
- +447876545132
- Rotherham, South Yorkshire, UK
- in https://www.linkedin.com/i n/zachary-owen-46a1b0b6/
- https://github.com/DeadEnigma13

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Python

JavaScript

JQuery

SOL

APIS

Bootstrap

Agile

LANGUAGES

English German



AWARDS

Code Institute 5 Day Coding Challenge 2022-04-06 Code Institute

Zack Owen

FULL STACK DEVELOPER STUDENT

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer currently enrolled in a Diploma in Full Stack Development from Code Institute. I have the ability to produce clean, maintainable and re-usable code. Experience building responsive websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript & Python as well as using frameworks like Bootstrap. Strong knowledge with using Git and GitHub. I possess strong communication and listening skills from 5 years' experience in a customer facing service role. Looking for a good opportunity as a Junior Full Stack Developer that will allow me to grow my portfolio and knowledge in the Software Industry.

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

The Feathered Duck Inn Website

May 2022 - Jun 2022

Developer

This project was designed as an interactive restaurant website made using Vanilla HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Customers can easily maneuver to different sections of the site to find information about the latest offers, menu, booking a table and even find the location of the restauarant.

- This portolio earned me a Merit grade for Project 1 of my Code Institute Full Stack Developer course.
- Live website: The Feathered Duck Inn
- GitHub Repository: Repository

2048 Interactive Game

Jul 2022 - Aug 2022

Developer

This project was designed as an interactive game called 2048 made using mostly JavaScript. The objective of the game was to try and create the 2048 tile by sliding the tiles in any direction.

- This portfolio earned me a Pass grade for Project 2 of my Code Institute Full Stack Developer course.
- Live website: 2048
- GitHub Repository: Repository

Hangman Interactive Game

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

Developer

This project was designed as an interactive game called Hangman made using Python. The objective of the game is to find the missing word by guessing a single letter before the hanging man is formed.

- This portfolio earned me Merit grade for Project 3 of my Code Insitute Full Stack Developer course.
- Live website: <u>Hangman Game</u>
- GitHub Repository: Repository

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Mobile Service Technician

Jun 2018 - Present

Henry Schein UK

- Developed and mentored new upcoming service technicians.
- Troubleshooted and fault found problems with equipment and devices used in the industry.
- Maintained new and old technologies and equipment to a sufficeent standard.
- Liased with managers and customers with new ideas and/or the latest idea in which will benefit both the business and their own customers.
- Reduced downtime of customers equipment with effective repairs and resolutions.
- Partnered with other engineers to complete much bigger projects successfully

Apprentice Electrical Engineer

Oct 2015 - Jun 2018

Contained Air Solutions Ltd

- Raised any problems with the manager/supervisor about the various different classes of cabinets.
- Diagnosed faults and problems without any further complications or damages.
- Tested and installed various devices which required short deadlines to maintain company goals and customer satisfaction.

EDUCATION

Diploma of Higher Education in Full Stack Development

Code Institute

HTML5, CSS, Python, JavaScript, SQL, JQuery, Bootstrap, APIs, Agile

Diploma of Higher Education in Electrical/Electronic Engineering

Oldham Training Centre

Diploma of Higher Education in Testing & Inspecting Of Electrical Equipment

Oldham Training Centre

NVQ Diploma in Engineering Oldham Training Centre

Oct 2015 - Dec 2018

Iul 2018 - Oct

2020

May 2022 - Present

Dec 2018 - Oct 2020